{
    "testers": [
        "fred.miller097@gmail.com",
        "fredfishgames@gmail.com"
    ],
    "admins": [
        "fred.miller097@gmail.com"
    ],
    "authorizedDomains": [
        "orleanspark.school"
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One million electrons travel between two points in a circuit.\nThe total energy gained by the electrons is 1.6x10<sup>-10</sup>J.\n\nWhat is the potential difference between the two points?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "1.6x10<sup>-16</sup>V",
                "1.6x10<sup>-4</sup>V",
                "1.0x10<sup>3</sup>V",
                "1.0x10<sup>9</sup>V"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is <strong>not</strong> a unit of energy?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "answers": [
                "kWh",
                "eV",
                "J",
                "W"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 3"
        },
        {
            "question": "A progressive wave of amplitude a has intensity <em>I</em>. This wave combines with another wave of amplitude 0.6 <em>a</em> at a point in space. The phase difference between the waves is 180°.\n\n What is the resultant intensity of the combined waves in terms of <em>I</em>",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "answers": [
                "0.16 <em>I</em>",
                "0.4 <em>I</em>",
                "1.6 <em>I</em>",
                "2.6 <em>I</em>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 0,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stationary waves are produced in a tube closed at one end and open at the other end. The fundamental frequency is 120 Hz.\n\nWhat is a possible frequency for a harmonic for this tube?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "answers": [
                "60 Hz",
                "240 Hz",
                "360 Hz",
                "480 Hz"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 6"
        },
        {
            "question": "A capacitor discharges through a resistor. At time t = 0, the charge stored by the capacitor is 600 μC. The capacitor loses 5.0 % of its charge every second.\n\nWhat is the charge left on the capacitor at time t = 4.0 s?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "111 μC",
                "120 μC",
                "480 μC",
                "489 μC"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3,
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which statement is correct?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "Hadrons are made up of protons and neutrons.",
                "A positron and a proton are examples of leptons.",
                "The positron and the electron have the same mass.",
                "The weak nuclear force is responsible for alpha decay."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 10"
        },
        {
            "question": "An electron moves in a circle of radius 2.0 cm in a uniform magnetic field of flux density 170 mT.\n\nWhat is the momentum of this electron?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "3.4 × 10<sup>−3</sup>kgms<sup>−1</sup>",
                "5.4 × 10<sup>−17</sup>kgms<sup>−1</sup>",
                "1.4 × 10<sup>−18</sup>kgms<sup>−1</sup>",
                "5.4 × 10<sup>−22</sup>kgms<sup>−1</sup>"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 3,
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 11"
        },
        {
            "question": "A beam of charged particles is not deflected when it passes through a region where both electric and magnetic fields are present.\n\nWhich statement is <strong>not</strong> correct?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "All the particles have the same speed.",
                "The resultant force on each particle is zero.",
                "The magnetic force is equal to the electric force on each particle.",
                "The magnetic field and the electric field are in the same direction."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 0,
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 13"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are four important attenuation mechanisms by which X-ray photons may interact when they pass through matter.\n\nIn which mechanism is the X-ray photon scattered with a longer wavelength?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "simple scattering",
                "Compton effect",
                "pair production",
                "photoelectric effect"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "timeLimit": 60,
            "exam": "H556/02 June 2017 Question 14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these statements are <strong>true</strong> about X-Rays?\nA) They are affected by a magnetic field\nB) They are electromagnetic waves\nC) They are used in CAT scans",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "A, B and C are correct",
                "Only B and C are correct",
                "Only C is correct",
                "Only B is correct"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "timeLimit": 60
        },
        {
            "question": "An ultrasound transducer emits ultrasound towards a baby at 20kHz.\nThe detector detects pulses at t=30μs and t=85μs.\n\nThe speed of ultrasound in the head is 1.5x10<sup>3</sup> m s<sup>-1</sup>\n\n What is the size of the head?",
            "type": "EXAM",
            "answers": [
                "7.5cm",
                "8.2cm",
                "8.1cm",
                "10.3cm"
            ],
            "correctAnswer":1,
            "timeLimit": 60
        } 
    ]
}